

Dostonbek Soliyev

Software engineer

As a strong believer in the ability of problem-solving and research combined with critical thinking, I approach every coding challenge as an opportunity to innovate and elevate. My journey in programming is marked by a commitment to continuous learning, adapting to emerging technologies, and a dedication to producing solutions that not only meet requirements but exceed expectations. r

rruzibayevich@gmail.com

Tashkent, Uzbekistan

github.com/ruziba3vich

+998 90 290 90 12

in linkedin.com/in/dostonbek-soliyev-89bb77283

stackoverflow.com/users/22318271/prodonik

EDUCATION

Digital economy

Ferghana branch of Tashkent University of Information Technologies

09/2022 - Present Ferghana

Courses

Programming 1
Programming 2
Differential equations
Entry into Webprogramming

 Discrete structures
Data Structures and Algorithms

Bootcamp(Foundation)

Najot ta'lim

07/2023 - 11/2023 Ferghana

Courses

- Basics of C - Entry to Python

Object Oriented Programming(OOP)
Desktop applications via PyQt
Entry to databases(MySQL)
Data Structures and Algorithms

Bootcamp(Golang)

Najot ta'lim

03/2024 - Present Tashkent

Courses

GolangREST and RESTful APIACID

Microservices(rpc, JSONrpc and gRPC) - Gin framework

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant teacher

Najot ta'lim

03/2024 - Present Tashkent

Contact: Sayyidolimxon Maksumov - +998 90 097 97 11

ENGAGEMENTS

Leetcode (04/2023 - Present) https://leetcode.com/u/prodonik/

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Online job platform - a platform for finding job vacancies (only the back-end part built on gRPC) (06/2024 - Present)

git@github.com:ruziba3vich/online_job_application.git

Tarkib uz - a web site for learning new receipts of dishes (02/2024 - Present)

tarkib.uz

CERTIFICATES

Master the fundamentals: Python for beginners (11/2023 - Present)

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-f96e8c27-af9a-4c27-b00c-5908231e4d22.jpg?v=1699801715000

Beginners guide into Python (11/2023 - Present)

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-f77cc30e-59f6-486b-97f8-ed1721b754d1.jpg?v=1699793524000

ACHIEVEMENTS

Robocontest Round #83 (09/2023 - Present) 43rd place among 326 participants

1st place at algorithms competition at najottalim (04/2024 - 05/2024)

LANGUAGES

English Uzbek

Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Russian

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding | Ping Pong |

Football